## **OBJECTIVE**

Dedicated individual with a proactive approach and a background in engineering and computer science in search of a position wherein I can apply experience and technical skills & knowledge towards a long-term career in a challenging technical position.









## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Computer Science graduate offering a strong foundation in software engineering and programming principles with over 5 years' experience in engineer-minded project focus. Currently responsible for supporting projects and various engineering tasks within a research & development team working on medical devices. Additional experience with installing, configuring, and troubleshooting electrical and mechanical systems.

### Skills

Languages: Java, SQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python

Platforms/ Frameworks: Ruby/Rails, SQL Server, MongoDB, Node.js, Git, Microsoft Office. Linux/Unix

Other: Critical Thinking, Collaboration, Communication, Web Development, Coding

## **Education**

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science, Kennesaw State University GPA 3.76/4.00 – December 2018

Relevant Course Work: Advanced Database, Linux/Unix Administration, Internet Programming, Intro to Software Engineering, Algorithm Analysis, Software Architecture and Design, Operating Systems, Software System Requirements

Associate of Applied Science, Electronic/Computer Engineering Technology, Chattahoochee Technical College GPA 3.97/4.00 – 2011.

#### **Portfolio**

Making My Own Sunshine Blog – Ruby on Rails: Blog website where users login to create new articles and upload images using an open source text editor.

Project Muser – MERN Stack: Application that turns home computer into a server where users can access their music anywhere over the internet.

KSU Bookstore – ASP.NET: Mock website where users can search and purchase books based on their class schedule.

#### Honors/Awards

Upsilon Pi Epsilon Honor Society Member - International Honor Society for the Computing and Information Disciplines

Boston Scientific 2016 Engineering Excellence Award

## **Experience**

Boston Scientific, Alpharetta, GA November 2013 - Present

# R&D Specialist

- Development of verification and validation test methods, protocols, and reports in an FDA regulated industry.
- Project support by performing various tasks in relation to product design, process development, fixture design, design verification testing, prototype building, FMEA analysis, design reviews, etc.

FLIR Integrated System, Alpharetta, GA July 2012 – November 2013 Electrical/Mechanical Technician

# RE/MAX Regional Services, Alpharetta, GA May 2011 – June 2012

Technical Services Coordinator

- Provided day-to-day contact for users, actively sought out resolution to user problems with designated product/ service lines and trained numerous remote offices on company provided software platforms.
- Provided office network support for servers, computers/laptop, printer/copier, etc